Okay, so let's talk about the course budget.
So there is a cost associated with using this course because using the AWS AI services is not free.
If you follow along with me and do the hands-on, you will incur charges,
but I do my best to guide you on how to limit them and I show you what will cost you money and how to turn things off.
Now, as you see though, I've spent all my course recording 31 cents, so it's not a lot,
but 14 different services having incurred cost and of course, if you don't follow closely,
and then all of a sudden you leave things running or you do use something too much,
your courses cost are going to go up.
So I want to give you a little of a heads-up here just to make sure that nothing unexpected happens to you.
Some services, for example, Amazon Q, have three trials, but again with your trials is dangerous because you don't forget to turn it off
and then you have charges, so I will again show you how to turn things off, of course.
But very good for you to triple check things in your case.
So to make it extra safe, I'm going to show you in the next lecture,
how to set up a course budget and you set the alarm to whatever amount you feel comfortable,
so that you make sure that in case you hit your course budget, in case you have a forecast of hitting your course budget,
then you'll receive an email notification and you can have a look at your bill to see what is costing you money.
So that's it for this lecture. I hope you liked it and I will see you in the next lecture.